OK
Account
Accounts
Edit account
Delete account
Open
Save
Edit
New
Delete
Undelete
Update mailboxes
Configuration
Buy and unlock
Tools
File Explorer
Program update
Address Book
Welcome!
No e-mail account is defined. Do you want set up e-mail account now?
Rules
Rule
<add condition>
Subject begins with:
Subject contains:
Sender begins with:
Sender contains:
"To:" contains:
Size is less than:
Size is more than:
Age less than:
Age more than:
Spam score less
Spam score more
Sender is Contact
Sender not Contact
Low priority
High priority


days
Mark for deleting
Delete immediately
Get header only
Get entire body
Set Low priority
Set High priority
Hide message
Move to Folder
Download part of message
Play alert
Assign color

IF
AND
OR
Operator
Add condition
Delete condition
About


Mailbox
Message
Update mailbox
Send messages
Download bodies
Download
Download all
Mark
Selected
All
None
As read
As unread
Hide
Unhide
Sort by
Reply
Reply all
Forward
New message
Attachment
Add to contacts
Reply from account...
Open link
Show link
Save target as...
Scroll
Page up
Page down
Enable
Disable
Move up
Move down
Account to use
Connect
Disconnect
Connecting
Disconnecting
Compose message
Account name
Name of account.
E-mail address
E-mail address associated with account.
Display name
This name will be displayed as sender name in messages that you send.
Mail server type
Type of incoming mail server.
Incoming mail server
Server for incoming mail messages (POP3/IMAP).
Outgoing mail server
Server used for sending mail (SMTP).
Username
Username used to logon to your mail or smtp server.
Password
Password used to logon to your mail or smtp server.
Access point
Internet access point to use for connection. If you choose automatic, you'll be asked to select one during connecting.
Get entire message
If checked, entire messages are downloaded during mailbox update (otherwise only new headers are retrieved).
Include in Update
If enabled, this account will be updated when performing "Update mailboxes" from Main screen.
Advanced settings
Advanced account configuration.
SMTP authentication
Enable if your SMTP server requires user authentication using username / password.
SMTP username
If SMTP authentication is enabled, this username will be used to log-on. If it is blank, the username of incoming server is used.
SMTP password
Password used for SMTP authentication. If it is blank, the password of incoming server is used.
POP3 port
Port to use for incoming mail server. If it is blank, then standard port will be used (110, or 995 for SSL connection).
SMTP port
Port to use for outgoing mail server. If it is blank, then standard port will be used (25).
Use SSL for POP3
Use secure connection for communication with incoming mail server.
Use SSL for SMTP
Use secure connection for communication with outgoing mail server.
Secure POP3 login
Use secure password transfer (using APOP command) when connecting to POP3 account.
IMAP port
Port to use for incoming mail server. If it is blank, then standard port will be used (143, or 993 for SSL connection).
Use SSL for IMAP
Use secure connection for communication with incoming mail server.
Send Bcc copy to:
Send hidden copy of sent messages to specified e-mail address.
Use STARTTLS
Use STARTTLS server command for secure (SSL) SMTP connection.
Enter account name.
Enter valid e-mail address.
Enter mail server name.
Sent
Saved
Open by System
File
Select
Rename
Make Dir
Extract to...
By e-mail
Show
Hidden files
ROM drives
Send by
E-mail
Bluetooth
Infrared
Sending
File sent:
Name:
e-mail:
Cut
Copy
Paste
Move
Sent:
Recv.:
Data counters
Reset counters
<deleted message>
<body not retrieved>
<automatic>
Show details
Message details
Show hidden
Drive details
Drive
Folder details
Folder
File details
Size
Modify date
Number of folders:
Number of files:
Total size:
Bytes
Hidden
Read-only
Please wait...
Opening...
Copying...
Moving...
Save as:
Choose file:
Initializing...
Logging in...
New header:
New message:
Downloading...
Deleting
Getting body
Messages:
No messages
Canceling...
Sending
Message
Failed to connect
Connection time-out
Invalid user/password
No such message
Can't create dir:
Can't rename file:
Can't send file:
Not found:
Connection failed:
Trial usage expired. Please register the program.
Mail server doesn't support secure (APOP) login. Disable secure login is account settings.
Sort messages by:
Message sorting option. This affects all accounts.
Date
Subject
Sender
Sort direction:
Messages sorting direction.
Ascending
Descending
Show data counter
If enabled, data counter is displayed when sending or receiving data.
None
Total
Current session
Connection time-out:
Time after which non-responding connection is closed (timed-out).
Sec
Min
Disabled
Text font size
Font used when displaying texts (when reading or writing messages, or reading text).
UI font size
Font size used for user interface.
Small
Normal
Big
Show message preview
Enable preview of message in mailbox browser.
Color theme
Color variation used in the program.
Download attachments
Download attachments during downloading message text.
Send immediately
If enabled, messages are sent immediately, otherwise they're queued and sent when updating mailbox.


Download HTML images
Download images in HTML messages from the Internet.


Save sent messages
Save messages that you sent to the Sent mailbox.
Date format
Format how date is displayed. DD = day, MM = month, YY = year.
Auto-update time
Time period, after which accounts are automatically updated (in minutes). Leave blank to disable.
Notification sound
Sound played when new messages are fetched.
Notification volume
Volume of notification sound, in range 0-10. To disable notification, set this to zero.
Language
Application language.
Keep connection
If checked, connection will be kept active while program runs, otherwise connection is closed after short time.
Subj:
------- Original message -------
From:
To:
Sent:
Date:
Time:
Send
Save as draft
Cancel writing
Add attachment
Browse attachments
Remove attachment
Add recipient
Priority
Low
Normal
High
Fit to screen
Original size
Zoom in
Zoom out
Error!
Delete account
Delete message
Delete marked
Are you sure?
Delete file?
Delete folder?
Delete selected?
Invalid recipient:
Invalid e-mail:
Add recipients!
Can't open file:
Can't delete file:
Can't write to file:
Disk full!
Not enough memory.
No viewer found:
Overwrite file?
Delete contact?
Delete rule?
Delete condition?
Yes
No
Cancel
Exit
Back
Done
Menu
free
Buy and unlock ProfiMail. To purchase license key, please visit:
After purchase, the application will be unlocked automatically after first connection to Internet.
Device serial number:
Device user name:
Unlock key:
Trial usage left:
Invalid license key!
Registration successful! Thank you for purchase.
Signatures
Edit Signatures
Signatures Editor
Automatic update
Check now
Check for newer version now?
Your version:
Online version:
Your version is up to date
New version details:
Install update
Contact editor
First name
Last name
Email
Email 2
Email 3
Company
Mobile number
Telephone number
Write email
Folders
Folder
Refresh list
Retrieving folders...
Delete IMAP folder
Folder will be deleted on server. Are you sure?
Renaming IMAP folder
Creating IMAP folder
Move to Folder
Moving messages
Saving to server
Update all folders
If checked, all IMAP folders are updated. If cleared, only INBOX is updated.
Drafts folder name
Name of folder where Draft messages will be stored.
Trash folder name
Name of folder where deleted messages are stored.
Sent folder name
Name of folder where Sent messages will be stored.
Upload Sent messages
If checked, sent messages will be uploaded into mail server.
Root folder
IMAP root folder under which all your mail folders are located (e.g. 'Inbox').
Updating flags...
Message is Read
Message is Unread




Delete from device
This will delete message body from device, and the header will be hidden. Are you sure?
Download max. KB
Limit of kilobytes to download from message. Leave blank for no limitation.
||----------------|This is partially downloaded message.|Choose 'Download' from menu to download entire message.|
Select provider:
Other
User manual
Auto-start
Start application automatically when device starts.
Copy marked to:
Move marked to:
Previous
Next
Export settings
ProfiMail settings were exported to a file. This includes: Account settings, Rules and Signatures.
Import settings
This will import ProfiMail settings from saved file. Your Accounts, Rules and Signatures will be replaced by imported settings. Continue?
New settings were successfully imported.
Failed to import settings. The settings file may be corrupted, or from newer version that you have installed.
Program password
Password used to enter the application.
Enter password:
New password:
Current password:
Password set!
Password cleared!
Invalid password!
Alternative access point
Alternative Internet access point, used if connection to primary point fails. Example: set main IAP to Wifi, and alternative IAP to GPRS/EDGE.
Audio player
Length
Position
Volume
License is permanently fixed to this device.
License Agreement
Accept
Reject
Set flag
Clear flag
Automatically insert
Max days limit
Number of last x days, for which messages will be displayed/updated on your device. Leave blank to see all messages.
Copy from text
Search
Recipient
Search results
Text not found
Use Push email
Use Push email (IMAP IDLE) if server supports it.
Open image
Connect to Push email
How to connect to Push email (IMAP IDLE) enabled mailboxes at program startup.
Automatically
Manually
Ask
Connect to your IMAP mailboxes now?
Top
Bottom
Purge IMAP deleted messages
Automatically purge (remove from IMAP server) deleted messages.
Purge deleted
Push email
Connect all
Disconnect all
Full screen mode
Option to draw application in fullscreen mode, or to show system area.
IDLE ping time
How often (in minutes) is Push email (IMAP IDLE) connection sending keep-alive packet. Set lower if your IDLE connection disconnects.
Upload draft to IMAP server
Enable work times
Enable or disable ProfiMail working times. When disabled, email is synchronized without time limit.
Work times
Times when ProfiMail should check email automatically.
Start hour
Start hour when checking email begins.
End hour
End hour when checking email finishes.
Monday
Tuesday
Wednesday
Thursday
Friday
Saturday
Sunday
If enabled, email will be synchronized on this day.
Vibrate alert
Use vibration to notify about new messages.
Use system font
Use system font when checked, or own application font if unchecked.
Headers
Call number
Update existing
Data location
Location where program data (messages, attachments, rules, signatures) will be stored.
Location of program settings and data will be changed to %. Downloaded message bodies will be deleted. Continue?
Create folder
Make new folder as subfolder of "%" folder?
<root folder>
Previous version
Install previous version
Expand
Collapse
Only unread
Save all
Default
Push email connected
Scheduled mail check
Next mail check in % minutes
Next mail check:
Use Trash folder
Move deleted messages to Trash folder on server.
Header contains
Reply-to email
Optional email address where replies to sent messages should be sent to ("Reply-to" header field).
Entire thread
Threaded
Identities
Additional identities from which mail may be sent from this account.
Edit identity
Use identity
Copy link
Unread
No new messages
New message
Click to start
Try again?
Attempts left:
Account settings will be cleared now.
Diagnostic
Enable network logging
View log file
Send log to developer
Signature name
ProfiMail crashed
Please click here to send crash report.
An unexpected error occurred forcing ProfiMail to stop. Please help us fix this by sending us error data, all you have to do is click 'OK'.
You may also add your comments about the problem:
Sending crash report... Thank you.
